let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The miser gazed ...... at the pile of gold coins in front of him.",
    answer: "avidly",
    options: [
      "avidly",
      "admiringly",
      "thoughtfully",
      "earnestly"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "I haven't seen you ...... a week.",
    answer: "for",
    options: [
      "within",
      "since",
      "for",
      "from"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "...... water was in a jug so a crow survived",
    answer: "A little",
    options: [
      "A little",
      "Little",
      "A few",
      "Many"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Select the pair which has the same relationship.  GRAIN:SALT",
    answer: "chip:glass",
    options: [
      "shard:pottery",
      "shred:wood",
      "blades:grass",
      "chip:glass"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A person who does not believe in God",
    answer: "atheist",
    options: [
      "athiest",
      "fanatic",
      "theist",
      "heretic"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Antonym of protects is",
    answer: "deserts",
    options: [
      "defends",
      "deprives",
      "deserts",
      "secures"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Find the correct spelt word",
    answer: "adventitious",
    options: [
      "adventitious",
      "adventitous",
      "adventitus",
      "adventituous"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A hater of knowledge and learning is a",
    answer: "misologist",
    options: [
      "bibliophile",
      "philologist",
      "misogynist",
      "misologist"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Find the error in this sentence: Ram was / senior to / Sam in college",
    answer: "No error",
    options: [
      "Ram was",
      "senior to",
      "Sam in college",
      "No error"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Synonym of defer is",
    answer: "postpone",
    options: [
      "indifferent",
      "delay",
      "postpone",
      "defy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "State in which the few govern the many",
    answer: "Oligarchy",
    options: [
      "Monarchy",
      "Oligarchy",
      "Plutocracy",
      "Autocracy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Catching the train earlier will give us the ...... to do some shopping",
    answer: "chance",
    options: [
      "luck",
      "possibility",
      "occasion",
      "chance"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "A person who collects coins",
    answer: "numismatist",
    options: [
      "philatelist",
      "numismatist",
      "fatalist",
      "narcissist"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Synonym of delegate is",
    answer: "representative",
    options: [
      "officer",
      "representative",
      "member",
      "participant"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Find the correct spelt word.",
    answer: "Affidavit",
    options: [
      "Affedevit",
      "Affidevit",
      "Affidavit",
      "Afidevit"
    ]
  },

];

